{
  "puzzles" : [
{
  "id" : "",
  "type" : "math",
  "question" : "13 * 17",
  "choice" : {
   "a" : "271",
   "b" : "131",
   "c" : "151",
   "d" : "221"
 },
 "solution" : "d"
},

{
  "id" : "",
  "type" : "math",
  "question" : "8 * 23",
  "choice" : {
   "a" : "184",
   "b" : "214",
   "c" : "124",
   "d" : "174"
 },
 "solution" : "a"
},

{
  "id" : "",
  "type" : "math",
  "question" : "7 * 26",
  "choice" : {
   "a" : "252",
   "b" : "182",
   "c" : "122",
   "d" : "132"
 },
 "solution" : "b"
},
{
  "id" : "",
  "type" : "math",
  "question" : "15 * 5",
  "choice" : {
   "a" : "65",
   "b" : "30",
   "c" : "75",
   "d" : "92"
 },
 "solution" : "c"
},
{
  "id" : "",
  "type" : "math",
  "question" : "7 + 26",
  "choice" : {
   "a" : "33",
   "b" : "31",
   "c" : "34",
   "d" : "39"
 },
 "solution" : "a"
},
{
  "id" : "",
  "type" : "math",
  "question" : "19 * 3",
  "choice" : {
   "a" : "56",
   "b" : "49",
   "c" : "48",
   "d" : "57"
 },
 "solution" : "d"
},
{
  "id" : "",
  "type" : "math",
  "question" : "4 ^ 3",
  "choice" : {
   "a" : "16",
   "b" : "84",
   "c" : "64",
   "d" : "68"
 },
 "solution" : "c"
}
{
  "id" : "",
  "type" : "math",
  "question" : "22 * 11",
  "choice" : {
   "a" : "252",
   "b" : "242",
   "c" : "244",
   "d" : "212"
 },
 "solution" : "b"
},
{
  "id" : "",
  "type" : "math",
  "question" : "2 * 26",
  "choice" : {
   "a" : "52",
   "b" : "28",
   "c" : "24",
   "d" : "32"
 },
 "solution" : "a"
},
{
  "id" : "",
  "type" : "math",
  "question" : "5!",
  "choice" : {
   "a" : "15",
   "b" : "62",
   "c" : "120",
   "d" : "625"
 },
 "solution" : "c"
},
]
}